--- File: C:\Users\sunwo\AppData\Local\Temp\TravelKit_Final\CONTRIBUTING.md ---
   1: # Contributing to TravelKit
   2: 
   3: ## Core Rule (SSoT)
   4: - **All work MUST start from a GitHub Issue.**
   5: - No code/docs changes without an Issue that defines **Acceptance Criteria (PASS/FAIL)**.
   6: 
   7: ## Workflow (Issue -> PR -> Merge)
   8: 1. Create/choose an Issue and ensure it has:
   9:    - Description
  10:    - Acceptance Criteria (PASS/FAIL)
  11:    - No secrets/tokens/PII in text
  12: 2. Move the Issue label:
  13:    - status:backlog -> status:doing
  14: 3. Create a branch:
  15:    - git checkout -b <type>/<short-name>
  16: 4. Make changes and commit:
  17:    - Commit message should include context; PR body must link the Issue.
  18: 5. Create a PR:
  19:    - **PR body MUST include Closes #N or Fixes #N.**
  20: 6. Required Gate:
  21:    - 
  22: equire-linked-issue must be **SUCCESS** before merge.
  23: 7. Merge and close the loop:
  24:    - Merge PR
  25:    - Update Issue label: status:doing -> status:done
  26: 
  27: ## Templates
  28: - Use the repository templates:
  29:   - Issue templates: .github/ISSUE_TEMPLATE/*
  30:   - PR template: .github/PULL_REQUEST_TEMPLATE.md
  31: 
  32: ## Validation
  33: - Confirm required checks:
  34:   - gh pr view <PR> --json statusCheckRollup
  35: - Keep the repo clean:
  36:   - git status should be clean before switching tasks.
  37: 
  38: ## Security / Privacy (Hard Rule)
  39: - Never include secrets, tokens, API keys, passwords, or PII in:
  40:   - Issues, PRs, commit messages, logs, or generated excerpts.
  41: - Use secure environment variables and secret stores instead.
  42: 
--- File: C:\Users\sunwo\AppData\Local\Temp\TravelKit_Final\apps-script-samples\CONTRIBUTING.md ---
   1: # How to become a contributor and submit your own code
   2: 
   3: ## Contributor License Agreements
   4: 
   5: We'd love to accept your sample apps and patches! Before we can take them, we
   6: have to jump a couple of legal hurdles.
   7: 
   8: Please fill out either the individual or corporate Contributor License Agreement
   9: (CLA).
  10: 
  11: * If you are an individual writing original source code and you're sure you
  12:   own the intellectual property, then you'll need to sign an
  13:   [individual CLA](https://developers.google.com/open-source/cla/individual).
  14: * If you work for a company that wants to allow you to contribute your work,
  15:   then you'll need to sign a
  16:   [corporate CLA](https://developers.google.com/open-source/cla/corporate).
  17: 
  18: Follow either of the two links above to access the appropriate CLA and
  19: instructions for how to sign and return it. Once we receive it, we'll be able to
  20: accept your pull requests.
  21: 
  22: ## Contributing A Patch
  23: 
  24: 1. Submit an issue describing your proposed change to the repository in question.
  25: 1. The repository owner will respond to your issue promptly.
  26: 1. If your proposed change is accepted, and you haven't already done so, sign a Contributor License Agreement (see details above).
  27: 1. Fork the desired repository, develop and test your code changes.
  28: 1. Ensure that your code adheres to the existing style in the sample to which you are contributing.
  29: 1. Ensure that your code has an appropriate set of unit tests which all pass.
  30: 1. Run `pnpm check` to ensure there are no type errors or syntax issues in your `.gs` files.
  31: 1. Submit a pull request!
  32: 
  33: ## Style
  34: 
  35: Samples in this repository follow the [JavaScript Semi-Standard
  36: Style](https://github.com/Flet/semistandard).
